Guide to the International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences Records 1970-1984
University of Chicago Library
- Series VIII: Publication Materials
  - Subseries 4: Conference Papers and Original Drafts
    - DH-DZ, Dhalla, Homi B., conference paper, 1973 Dinerman, Ina R., conference paper, 1973 Dmitieva, S.I., conference paper, 1973 Dobbert, Marion L., draft, 1973 Doi, Takuji, draft, 1973 Domotor, ?, draft, 1973 Dredge, C. Paul, draft, 1973 Drobizheva, L.H., conference paper, 1973 Dubreuil, Guy and E.D. Wittkower, conference paper, 1973 Ducey, Paul R., conference paper, 1973 Dumett, Raymond E., conference paper, 1973 Dumitrescu, H. conference paper and translation, 1973 Du Toit, Brian M., conference paper, 1973 Dunare, Nicolas, conference paper, 1973 Dzharylgasinova, R. Sh., conference paper, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - David, Kenneth, drafts, undated (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - David, Kenneth, drafts, undated (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Dervyanko, A.P., draft, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Dillon, Wilton S., reprint, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Divalo, William Julio, draft, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Dominguez, Alfred Mendez and Gordon Darrow, conference paper, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Dredge, C. Paul, draft, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - E, Ecsedy, Csaba, conference paper, 1973 Eisenstadt, S.N., conference paper, 1973 El-Hakin, Sherif and John Markoff, conference paper, 1973 Ellis, David V., conference paper, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Ehrhardt, Anke A., draft, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Elahi, K., draft, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Faris, J.C., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Fedorova, S.G., conference paper, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Formozov, A.A., conference paper, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Freedman, Maurice, draft, session 721, 1973 and introductory remarks by Fred Eggan, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - GA-GI, Gamburd, Geraldine, conference papers, 1973 Ganguly, Pranab, draft and conference paper, 1973 García, María-Pilar, and Rae Lesser Blumberg, conference paper, 1973 Gardner, Louise, conference paper, 1973 Garine, Igor de Gavazzi, M., draft, 1973 Gearing, Frederick, draft, 1973 Gedicks, Al, draft, 1973 George, J.E., conference paper, 1973 Gessain, Monique, conference paper, 1973 Gessain, R., conference paper and translations, 1973 Ghosh, Asok K., conference paper, 1973 Gilber, Vera Jane, draft, 1973 Giles, Howard and Richard Bourhis, conference paper, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - GO-GU, Goldberg, Harvey E., Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Goldberg-Mulkiewicz, Olga, Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Goldstein, Melvyn C., Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 González, G. and M.M. Errázuris, Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Gooch, Donald R., Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Gordon, Robert J. and Wade C. Pendleton, Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Gráfik, Imre, Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Gravaris, I. and M. Giessen, draft, undated Grimm, H., Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Griva, Edelmi E. draft, 1973 Gunawardena, K.L, Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 Guseva, N.R., Gurvich, I.S., abstract, 1973 Gutierrez, Ramon, conference paper, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Gedicks, Al, draft, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Goldberg, Harvey E., Gurvich, I.S., conference paper, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Güttgemanns, Erhardt, draft, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - HA, Haas, Marilyn L., draft, 1973 Haque, Abu Saeed Zahurul, draft, 1973 Hartle, Donald D., conference paper, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - HE-HO, Haskell, Edward, draft, 1973 Heath, Barbara Honeyman, conference paper, 1973 Heilfurth, Gerhard, conference paper and translation, 1973 Heinrich, Albert, conference paper, 1973 Henderson, M.C., conference paper, 1973 Henrotte, J.G., conference paper, 1973 Hirschfeld, Gerhard, conference paper, 1973 Hirschfeld, William J. and Robert M. Moyers, conference paper, 1973 Holmes, Lowell D., conference paper, 1973 Howard, Alan and Irwin Howard, draft, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Hr-I, Hrissanfova, E.N., conference paper, 1973 Hunte, Pamela A., conference paper, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Halanaka, S., draft, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Harris, Richard M., 1974 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Hassan, Fekri, A., 1973 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Hassan, Riaz and Geoffry Benjamin, draft, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Heilfarth, Gerhard, draft, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Hirschfeld, Gerhard, draft, introduction and conference paper, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Hockings, Paul, conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Hoffer, Carol P., draft, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - I, Ikegami, Yoshihiko, conference paper, 1973 Inal-Ipa, Sh.D., conference paper, 1973 Inouye, Teruko, draft, 1973 Isaac, Glynn L., conference paper, 1973 Islam, Mazharul, conference paper, 1973 Ismagulov, O., conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Idris-Soven, Elizabeth, conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Ikawa-Smith, Fumiko, conference paper and correspondence, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Ikawa-Smith, Fumiko, conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Ingman, Stanley and Anthony Thomas, draft and correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Irving, W. conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Irving, William, editorial notes and correspondence, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - JA, Jaeger, Georges, conference paper, 1973 Jagannadhacharyulu, C., conference paper, 1973 Jairazbhoy, R.A., draft, undated Jansen II, William H., conference paper, 1973 Jason, Heda, conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - JE-JU, Jenkins, Trefor and G.T. Nurse, draft, 1973 Johnson, Donald Lee, draft, 1973 Johnson, Frank A. and Anthony Marsella, conference paper, 1973 Jones, Steven H., draft, 1973 Jürgens, H.W., draft, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Jack Jr., Lenus, draft, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Anthony, draft, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Jacob, Teuku, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Jacobs, Ruth Harriett, draft, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Jacobs, Sue-Ellen, conference paper, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Jacobson, Doranne, draft, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Jácome, Nicanor and Inés Llumiquinga, draft, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Jaeger, Georges, conference paper, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Jagannadhacharyulu, C. draft. 1973 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - James, Hermann, draft, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Jankowsky, Walter G., reprint, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Jánossy, Dénes, draft, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Jansen, William Hugh, draft, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Janzen, John M., draft, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Jason, H., abstract, correspondence, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Jason, H., draft, correspondence, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Jason, Helda, draft, conference paper, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Jean, Zoanga Bigtarma, conference paper, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Jeffreys, M.D.W., draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Jelínek, Jan, conference paper, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Jenkins, Farish, A., draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Jenkins, Trefor, draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Jennings, George J., draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Jerome, Norge W. draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Jest, C., conference paper, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Jilek, Wolfgang G., draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Jilek-Aall, Louise, draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, T. draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, L. Lewis, draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Johnsons, Frank A., conference paper, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Johnston, Elizabeth, and Watts, reprints and correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Johnston, Elizabeth, and Watts, reprints and correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Johnston, Francis E. draft. 1973 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Jolly, Grace, draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Joshi, Om Prakash, draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Jürgens, H.W., draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - KA-KE, Kabo, V.R., conference paper, 1973 Kadetotad, N.K., conference paper, 1973 Kagan, Zippora, conference paper, 1973 Kahlon, D.P.S., draft, 1973 Kalinovskaya, K.P., conference paper, 1973 Kanai, Tenbi, conference paper, 1973 Karakeev, K.G., conference paper, 1973 Karim, Anwarul, draft, 1973 Katona, Imre, conference paper, 1973 Kauffman, Robert, conference paper, 1973 Keesing, Roger M., conference paper, 1973 Keur, Dorothy and Russell LaDae, draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - KH-KO, Kikuchi, Yasushi, conference paper, 1973 Kim, Won-Yong, conference paper, 1973 Kisliakov, N.A., conference paper, 1973 Kiyatikina, T.P., conference paper, 1973 Klein, L.S., conference paper, 1973 Klymasz, Robert B., draft, 1973 Kochiyev, R.S., conference paper, 1973 Koechlin, Bernard, draft, 1973 Konstantinovi, Vesna D., conference paper, 1973 Kopczynska-Jaworska, B., conference paper and translation, 1973 Kozhin, P.M., conference paper, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - KR-KU, Kresz, Mária, conference paper, 1973 Kriukov, M.V., conference paper, 1973 Krondl, M.M. and G.G. Boxen, conference paper, 1973 Kryvelev, I.A., conference paper, 1973 Kubik, Gerhard, draft, 1973 Kudrjavtzev, M.K., conference paper, 1973 Kumanyov, V.A., conference paper, 1973 Kurais II, Muhammad, conference paper, 1973 Kurshakova, Y.S., conference paper, 1973 Kutrzeba-Pojnarowa, Anna, conference paper, 1973 Kuznetsov, A.I., conference paper, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Kabo, V.R., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Kabwegyere, T.B., draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Kadetotad, N.K., draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Kagan, Ziporra, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Kalab, M., draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Kalinovskaya, K.P., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Kaloyev, B.A., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Kahlke, H.D., draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Kamau, I.J., draft, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Karim, Anwarul, drafts and correspondence, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Katz, Solomon H., draft, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Kendon, Adam, draft and correspondence, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Kessler, Carolyn, draft, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Keur, Dorothy and Russell La Due, draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Khalil, Zamiti, draft and correspondence, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Khare, R.S., drafts, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Khazanov, A.M. (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Khubchandani, Lachman M., draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - King, A.D., draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - King, J. and A.E. Tregunza, draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Klymasz, Robert B., draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Knez, Gene (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Knezevic, Srebrica, drat and conference paper, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Kohn de Brief, Fritzi, draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Koo, Jang H., draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Korompay, Bertalan, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Kosova, María, draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Kozhin, P.M., 1972 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Kozlov, V.I., 1973 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Kralovānszley, A., draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Krantz, Grover S., draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Kresz, M., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Kurais II, Muhamad, draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Kwei, H.L., reprint, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - LA, Lareng, L. and R. Giacardy, conference paper, 1973 Lavell, Cherry, conference paper, 1973 Lavondés, Anne, draft and conference paper, 1973, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - LE, Ledoux, Geneviéve and André Lepage, conference paper, 1973 Lee, Du Hyun, draft, 1973 Lefevre-Witier, Ph., and H. Vergnes, conference paper, 1973 Leibowitz, Lila, draft, 1973 Levine, Morton H., and Victoria von Hagen, conference paper, 1973 Levin, Stephen K., conference paper, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - LI-LO, Light Jr., Donald W., conference paper, 1973 Lima, Mequitela, draft, 1973 Lindenfeld, Jacqueline, conference paper, 1973 Loflin, Marvin D., draft, 1973 Loots, Willie, draft, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - LU-LW, Lucas, Jack A., draft, 1973 Luomala, Katherine, draft, 1973 Lwanga-Lunyiigo, S., draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Lah, Maria, draft, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Lebeuf, A.M.D, publication, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Leeds, Anthony, draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Leeson, Joyce, conference paper, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Lefevre-Witier, Ph., and H. Vergnes, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Lindenfeld, Jacqueline, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Lipschutz, Alexander, draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Lomax, Alan, draft and conference papers, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Loveland, Franklin, draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - MA-MAL, MacCormack, C.P.H, draft, 1973 Maddox, Darryl N., conference paper, 1973 Machado Bonet, Ofelia, conference paper and translations, 1973 MacLachlan, Bruce B., conference paper, 1973 Magli, Ida, conference paper, 1973 Mahler, Fred, draft, 1973 Maier, Radu Octavian, draft, 1973 Maier, R.O., draft, 1973 Makarius, Raoul, conference paper and translation, 1973 Makesetov, K.M., conference paper, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - MAM-MAZ, Maretina, S.A., conference paper, 1973 Marinov, Vasil, conference papers and translation, 1973 Markova, L.V., conference paper, 1973 Mars, L., conference paper, 1973 Mateesco, Cornelius N., conference paper and translation, 1973 Mathur, H.M., draft, 1973 Matzdorff, Ingrid, conference paper and translation, 1973 Mauran-Sendrail, A. and Ph. Lefevre-Witier, conference paper, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - ME-MOO, Melikishvili, G.A., conference paper, 1973 Melko, Matthew, conference paper, 1973 Michel, Guillermo, draft, 1973 Miller, Elmer S., conference paper, 1973 Miller, Ron, draft, 1973 Mitchell, Edna, conference paper, 1973 Moberg, Carl-Axel, conference paper, 1973 Mochanov, Y.A., conference paper, 1973 Monnet, A. and Y. Cabadi, conference paper, 1973 Morgan, John Henry, conference paper, 1973 Mis (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - MOR-MY, Moraru-Popa, Georgeta, draft, undated Morsy, Ahmed, draft, 1973 Mosimann, James E., draft, 1973 Mukherjeee, Prabhati, draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Mabuchi, T. draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Madsen, Peter, reprint, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Mahapatra, Sitakant, draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Makarius, Kaoul, draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Maksetov, K.M., draft, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Malhotra, K.C., draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Mallik, B.P., draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Markarian, E.S., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Paul, draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Maruyama, Mogorah, drafts, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Mateesco, Cornelius, Mansooruddin, M., abstract and draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Mazumder, Debika de, draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - McCadams, R., conference paper, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - McCormack, William C., conference paper and correspondence, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - McCormack, William, correspondence and Maher, J. Peter, draft, 1975-1978 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - McCormack, William, draft, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - McKean, Philip Frick, draft, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - McKee, H.L., draft 1973 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - McNeill, William H., reprint, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - McNeill, William H., correspondence and conference paper, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - McNeill, William H., conference paper, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Mead, Margaret, conference papers, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Melko, Matthew, draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Mencher, J.P., draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Miller, William C., draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Mishra, B.D., draft, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Misra, Bhabagrahi, and James Preston, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Mkrtumyan, Yu.I., draft, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Mladenovic, Olivera, draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Moberg, C.A., draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Monogarova, L.F., draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Monsooruddin, M., draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Morgan, John Henry, draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - N, Nakakuki, Masafumi, conference paper, 1973 Nance, Everette E., conference paper, 1973 Nemeskeri, Janos, draft, 1973 Nesbit, James, draft, 1973 Nettleship, Martin A., conference paper, 1973 Newcomer, M.H., draft, 1973 Newcomer, Peter Jay, conference paper, 1973 Newmeyer, Frederick J., conference paper, 1973 Nishimura, Asahitaro, draft, 1973 Nitityuk, B.A., conference paper, 1973 Nusbaum, Geoffrey, Nurge, Ethel, conference papers, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Nachtigall, Horst, draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Nag, Moni, draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Nash, J., and N. Hopkins, draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Nelson, Benjamin, reprint, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Newton, N., drafts, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Nishimura, Asahitaro (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Nurge, Ethel, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Nwa-chil, C.C., draft, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - O, Ohnuki-Tierney, Emiko, conference paper, 1973 Okladnikove, A.P., conference paper, 1973 Okoreaffia, C.O., conference paper, 1973 Orrurary, (?), draft, 1973 Ostric, Anthony, conference paper, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Ohyi, H., draft., 1973 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Okediji, Oladejo O., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Olea, Corona, draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Oledzki, Jacek, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Olusanya, Philip O., draft, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Orel, Jaroslav, conference paper, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Ostric, A, typescript, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Ottenberg, Simon, draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - PA-PE, Padan-Eisenstartk, Dorit, conference paper, 1973 Pawal, A. Raziq, draft, 1973 Papiha, S.S. and B.C. Chaparwal, conference paper, 1973 Parikos, Nicos, conference paper, 1973 Peng, Fred C.C., conference paper, 1973 Perabo, Fred, conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - PE-PI, Pescatello, A.M., and B.C. Wade, conference paper, 1973 Peshits, A.I., conference paper, 1973 Petrosyan, E.Kh., conference paper, 1973 Philippidou, H., conference paper, 1973 Pilotti, Francisco J., draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - PO-PU, Popescu, Alexandru, conference paper, 1973 Poplinsky, Yu.K., conference paper, 1973 Portéres, Roland, conference paper, 1973 Powlison, Paul S., conference paper, 1973 Pratap, D.R., conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Parilos, Nicos, conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Pattanyak, D.P., conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Petit-Skinner, Solange, draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Pilbeam, David, draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Pischel, Barbara, manuscript with illustrations, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Porras, Pedro I., draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Poulianos, A.N., draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Pride, J.B., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Putilove, B.N., conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Quinn, Frederick, conference paper, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - RA-RI, Radaza Demetrio, Francisco y, conference paper, 1973 Raffler Engel, Walburga von, draft, 1972 Rajbhandary, Heramba Bahadur, and Strughan Lal Pradhan, conference paper, 1973 Reeves, B.O.K., conference paper, 1973 Reshetov, A.M. Richards, Cara E., conference paper, 1973 Richkov, Y.G., and Sheremetieva, V.A., conference paper, 1973 Rios-Reyes, M., conference paper, 1973 Ritter, H.H. (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - RO-RY, Rodrigues, Lucio, draft, 1971 Rogers, Edward S., and James G.E. Smith, conference paper, 1973 Rohan-Csermak, G. de, conference paper, 1973 Rosinski, Franciszek M. and Anna Szwedzinska, draft and conference paper, 1973 Ross, D. Reid, draft, 1973 Ross, Jennie-Keith, conference paper, 1973 Rossi, Ino, conference paper, 1973 Rossi-Landi, Ferruccio, conference paper, 1973 Roy, P.K., conference paper, 1973 Rozhdestvenskaya, S.B., conference paper, 1973 Rumbaugh, Duane M., E.C. von Gasersfeldk, conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Rahim, S.A., draft, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Robakidze, A.I., draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Römer., B., conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Roy, M., conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Roper, Marilyn Keyes, draft, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Rosinski, F.M. (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Rubim de Pinho, Alvaro, draft and conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Russian scholar, no name, draft, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Rustad Sr., John, draft, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - SA, Safa, Helen I., conference paper, 1973 Saffirio, Luigi, conference paper, 1973 Saleh, Ahmed Rushdi, conference paper, 1973 Saliay, Keshari N., conference paper, 1973 Salivon, I.I., conference paper, 1973 Sarana, Gopāla, draft, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Sc-Sh, Scheflen, Albert E. conference paper, 1973 Schmidt, Richard Conrad, draft, 1973 Schneider, K.A., draft and conference paper, 1973 Schott, Lothar, conference paper, 1973 Scott, G.L., conference paper, 1973 Scotti, Piertro, draft, 1973 Sekelj, Tibor, conference paper, 1973 Sellnow, Irmgard, conference paper with translation, 1973 Sengupta, Syamalkanti, conference paper, 1973 Shahma, Abbimanuy, draft and conference paper, 1973 Sharma, Brahma Dev, conference paper, 1973 Sharma, Tarun, conference paper, 1973 Shasmal, Kartick Chandra, conference paper, 1973 Shchekochiknina, L.K., conference paper, 1973 Shmeleva, M.N., conference paper, 1973 Shendge-Zuberi, Malati, conference paper, 1973 Shur, L.A., conference paper, 1973 Sicard, Harald von, conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - SI-SM, Simionesco, Paul, draft, 1973 Simmons, D.R., conference paper, 1973 Simpson, Ruth Dee, conference paper, 1973 Singh, I.P., three drafts, 1973 Singh, Raghbir, draft, 1974 Slusser, Mary Shepard, conference paper, 1973 Smirnova, N.S., conference paper, 1973 Smith, Andrew, conference paper, 1973 Smith, David G., conference paper, 1973 Smith, Jason W., conference paper, 1973 Smith, Robert A., conference paper, 1973 Smith, Timothy J., conference paper, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - SO-ST, Sorenson, E. Richard, draft, 1973 Soudek, D., conference paper, 1973 Spitsin, V.A. conference paper, 1973 Spyridakis, Georgios, draft, 1973 Stagg, Ronald M., and William W. Vernon, conference paper, 1973 Stahl, Anca, conference paper, 1973 Stevens, Frank, conference paper, 1973 Strukelj, Pavla, conference paper, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - SU-SW, Suchý, Jaroslave, draft, 1973 Sukdeo, Fred, conference paper, 1973 Sukdeo, Iris, conference paper, 1973 Sumi, Tokan, conference paper, 1973 Sussi, Emidio, draft, 1973 Suzuki, Masao, conference paper, 1973 Sweet, Louise E., conference paper, 1973 Swiderski, Stanislaw, draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Sahlins, Marshall, conference paper, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Sankalia, H.D., draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Schaedel, Richard P., draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Schoepf, B.G., draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Sekelj, Tibor, draft, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Selier, Frits, J.M., draft, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Sengupta, D., draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Shankman, P., draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Sharma, Bramha Dev, draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Sharma, Turun, C., draft, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 12)